mobile-10.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy

The aim of this Privacy Policy is to inform users of how we collect and use certain information as a result of online advertising services provided by Mobile-10.com to its customers. 

## Our business

Mobile-10.com technology powers advertisements that can appear on websites and applications on mobile phones or other devices connected to the internet. You may interact directly with our servers (for example, when you click on an ad) or indirectly via the a web site or mobile application that displays the ads. 

## Commitment to Privacy

The European Union ("EU") maintains strict privacy laws through General Data Privacy Regulation ("GDPR") and protecting our customer's data is a main concern to ensure that we maintain the required compliance with the governing authorities. 

## Purpose of data collection

With each interaction between your device and our ad servers we collect certain information, which we will describe below. We use this information in order to help deliver more interesting and relevant ads to you, in order to provide to our customers and partners reports that contain aggregated data (for instance, the number of ads delivered each day, the number of clicks on those ads, and so on), in order to analyze trends, and in order to perform fraud detection. 

## Information collected

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you. We do, however, record and use information that is not personally identifiable, including but not limited to the following: 

  * the IP address of your device on the internet, to do geo-targeting, to identify your mobile operator, connection type, and other details;
  * the ‘user agent’ of your browser or application, and other relevant request headers, to help us identify your device type;
  * the date and time of the ad request or interaction;
  * and a unique identifier, such as an HTTP cookie or your device advertising identifier, that enables us not to show you the same ad over and over again.

We also encourage (but do not require) our publishers to share with us additional information that is not personally identifiable information, but that we may use in order to improve ad relevance. This data may include: 

  * your age or age range, if known to the publisher;
  * your gender, if known to the publisher;
  * your user geographic location, if known to the publisher.

From our partners, which include businesses, networks, agencies, publishers, and advertisers; we do collect personal information to identify the client to an account. The collection of this information is on a lawful basis, to which consent has been expressly given, and is part of Mobile-10.com normal business practices. These partners will be asked to provide personal information through the signup and registration process. This information is used to communicate the status of an account or billing and may include, but is not limited to: name, phone number, email address, website name, address and bank details. 

## Use of information

We may use this non personally identifiable information along with our technology in order to provide ads that are likely to be more interesting and more relevant to users to target advertising (this is also known as behavioral, or interest-based advertising). 

We sometimes use cookies or device identifiers to help us track whether you complete specific actions on an advertiser’s web site or application, as this is needed for analytical purposes, and in order to monitor the performance of our ads. These cookies or identifiers use the domain name "contextual-serving.com" and expire within 30 days. 

We may also use some of this data to provide interest-based advertising. 

## Opt-out

Opting Out is easy; when a you opt-out we will no longer be able to recognize and serve contextual or retargeted advertising to you. By you clicking on the opt-out button below, we will recognize that you are no longer are interested in receiving our advertising and will disable Mobile-10.com and its Partners the ability to deliver ads to you. 

## Your Data Rights

If you are in the EEA, you have a right to (subject to a limited number of exceptions): (i) request access to and rectification or erasure of your personal information; (ii) obtain restriction of processing or to object to processing of your personal information; and (iii) ask for a copy of your personal information to be provided to them, or a third party, in a digital format. You also have the right to lodge a complaint about the processing of your personal information with your local data protection authority in the EEA. 

If you are a client, and would like the personal information Mobile-10.com holds about you to be corrected or updated please contact affiliates@mobile-10.com. For the deletion and erasure of personal information, email affiliates@mobile-10.com to begin the process and we will respond to your request within 30 days. 

## The Protection of Minors

The Site does not knowingly collect any personal information from minors. The personal information of any minor you provide shall be agreed by the minor's parent or guardian in advance. Minor is defined in accordance with the laws applicable to the Privacy Policy. 

## Retargeting campaigns

We may run retargeting campaigns based on user lists provided directly by the advertisers, to reach a precise audience. 

## Marketing campaigns

We may contact our partners, which include businesses, networks, agencies, publishers, and advertisers; periodically by e-mail to provide information regarding our discounts, products, services and content that may be of interest to you. If applicable law requires that we receive your consent before we send you certain types of marketing communications, we will only send you those types of communications after receiving your consent. 

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, you may follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or request to be opted-out of receiving such communications via email to affiliates@mobile-10.com. 

## Changes to privacy policy

Mobile-10.com is committed to continually examining and reviewing its privacy practices, and may make changes to its Privacy Policy. In the event that material changes are made, the Privacy Policy on this website will be changed. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

Your continued use of the Site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you are acceptancing the consent and practices described in this policy and terms of use. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this Site. 

We use third-party cookies to measure and monitor the activity of the website accessible through the domain name mobile-10.com and its subdomains. Cookies policy
